1-2-Switch
10 Second Running RETURNS
12 orbits
1917 - The Alien Invasion DX
1979 Revolution: Black Friday
2064: Read Only Memories INTEGRAL
20XX
36 Fragments of Midnight
3D MiniGolf
60 Seconds!
6180 the moon
88 Heroes: 98 Heroes Edition
A Normal Lost Phone
A Robot Named Fight
A magical high school girl
ACA NEOGEO 2020 SUPER BASEBALL
ACA NEOGEO AERO FIGHTERS 2
ACA NEOGEO AERO FIGHTERS 3
ACA NEOGEO AGGRESSORS OF DARK KOMBAT
ACA NEOGEO BASEBALL STARS PROFESSIONAL
ACA NEOGEO BLAZING STAR
ACA NEOGEO CROSSED SWORDS
ACA NEOGEO FATAL FURY
ACA NEOGEO FOOTBALL FRENZY
ACA NEOGEO GAROU: MARK OF THE WOLVES
ACA NEOGEO GHOST PILOTS
ACA NEOGEO LAST RESORT
ACA NEOGEO LEAGUE BOWLING
ACA NEOGEO MAGICAL DROP II
ACA NEOGEO MAGICIAN LORD
ACA NEOGEO METAL SLUG
ACA NEOGEO METAL SLUG 2
ACA NEOGEO METAL SLUG 3
ACA NEOGEO METAL SLUG 4
ACA NEOGEO METAL SLUG X
ACA NEOGEO Money Puzzle Exchanger
ACA NEOGEO NEO TURF MASTERS
ACA NEOGEO NINJA COMBAT
ACA NEOGEO NINJA COMMANDO
ACA NEOGEO OVER TOP
ACA NEOGEO REAL BOUT FATAL FURY SPECIAL
ACA NEOGEO SAMURAI SHODOWN
ACA NEOGEO SAMURAI SHODOWN IV
ACA NEOGEO SENGOKU 2
ACA NEOGEO SENGOKU 3
ACA NEOGEO SHOCK TROOPERS
ACA NEOGEO SPIN MASTER
ACA NEOGEO SUPER SIDEKICKS 2
ACA NEOGEO SUPER SIDEKICKS 3 THE NEXT GLORY
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 2000
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 94
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 95
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 96
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 97
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 98
ACA NEOGEO THE KING OF FIGHTERS 99
ACA NEOGEO THE LAST BLADE 2
ACA NEOGEO THE SUPER SPY
ACA NEOGEO WAKU WAKU 7
ACA NEOGEO WORLD HEROES PERFECT
ACORN Tactics
AQUA KITTY UDX
ARK - Survival Evolved
ARMS
ATV Drift & Tricks
Ace of Seafood
Aces of the Luftwaffe - Squadron - Extended Edition
Aces of the Luftwaffe Squadron
Adventure Time - Pirates of the Enchiridion
Aegis Defenders
Agatha Knife
Air Conflicts Collection
Air Hockey
All-Star Fruit Racing
Alteric
Ambition of the slimes
America's Greatest Game Shows - Wheel of Fortune & Jeopardy!
American Ninja Warrior - Challenge
Angels of Death
Anima - Gate of Memories
Animal Rivals Switch
Animal Super Squad
Another Lost Phone: Lauras Story
Another World
Antiquia Lost
Ao no Kanata no Four Rhythm for Nintendo Switch
Aqua Moto Racing Utopia
Aragami - Shadow Edition
Arcade Archives 10-Yard Fight
Arcade Archives CRAZY CLIMBER
Arcade Archives City CONNECTION
Arcade Archives DONKEY KONG
Arcade Archives DOUBLE DRAGON
Arcade Archives HEROIC EPISODE
Arcade Archives Ikki
Arcade Archives Kid Niki Radical Ninja
Arcade Archives Kids Horehore Daisakusen
Arcade Archives MARIO BROS.
Arcade Archives MOON PATROL
Arcade Archives Ninja-Kid
Arcade Archives OMEGA FIGHTER
Arcade Archives PUNCH-OUT!!
Arcade Archives RYGAR
Arcade Archives Renegade
Arcade Archives STAR FORCE
Arcade Archives Sky Skipper
Arcade Archives TERRA CRESTA
Arcade Archives Traverse USA
Arcade Archives VS. SUPER MARIO BROS.
Asonde Igo ga Tsuyokunaru! Ginsei Igo DX
Assassin's Creed III Remastered
Asterix & Obelix XXL 2
Astro Bears Party
Astro Duel Deluxe
Atari Flashback Classics
Atelier Lulua - The Scion of Arland
Atelier Lydie & Suelle ~The Alchemists and the Mysterious Paintings~
Atelier Meruru Arland no Renkinjutsushi 3 DX
Atelier Rorona Arland no Renkinjutsushi DX
Atelier Totori Arland no Renkinjutsushi 2 DX
Attack on Titan 2
Axiom Verge
Azure Striker Gunvolt: Striker Pack
BAFL
BINGO for Nintendo Switch
BIOHAZARD 7 resident evil cloud version
BLEED
BLEED 2
BOOST BEAST
BUTCHER
Bad Dudes
BadNorth
Banner Saga
Banner Saga 2
Banner Saga 3
Baseball Riot
Bass Pro Shops - The Strike - Championship Edition
Bastion
Batman: The Telltale Series
Battle Chasers: Nightwar
Battle Chef Brigade
Battle Princess Madelyn
Bayonetta
Bayonetta 2
Beach Buggy Racing
Beat Cop
Behind The Screen
Ben 10
Bendy and the Ink Machine
Beyblade Burst - Battle Zero
Bibi & Tina - Adventures with Horses
Bibi Blocksberg - Big Broom Race 3
Big Buck Hunter Arcade
Billion Road
Binaries
Black The Fall
Blade Arcus Rebellion from Shining
Blade Strangers
Blaster Master Zero
BlazBlue - Central Fiction - Special Edition
BlazBlue - Cross Tag Battle
BlobCat
Bloodstained: Curse of the Moon
Bloody Zombies
Bloons TD 5
Blossom Tales
Boku no Hero Academia - One's Justice
Boku no Kanojo wa Ningyo-Hime! - My Girlfriend Is a Mermaid!
Bomb Chicken
Bomber Crew
Bomber Crew: Complete Edition
Bombslinger
Bouncy Bob
Bow to Blood: Last Captain Standing
Brave Dungeon + Dark Witchs Story:COMBAT
Brawl
Brawlout
Bridge Constructor Portal
Broforce
Broken Age
Broken Sword 5 - The Serpent's Curse
Bud Spencer & Terence Hill - Slaps And Beans
Bulb Boy
Cabela's - The Hunt - Championship Edition
Calculation Castle: Grecos Ghostly Challenge Addition
Calculation Castle: Grecos Ghostly Challenge Subtraction
Candle - The Power of the Flame
Carnival Games
Cars 3: Driven to Win
Cartoon Network - Battle Crashers
Castle of Heart
Castlestorm
Cat Quest
Cave Story+
Caveman Warriors - Deluxe Edition
Celeste
Cendrillon palikA
Chameleon Run Deluxe Edition
Champion Jockey Special
Chess Ultra
Chicken Range
Child of Light - Ultimate Edition + Valiant Hearts
Chocobo’s Mystery Dungeon - Every Buddy!
Chou Tousouchuu & Chou Sentouchuu Double Pack
Choukaiten Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido
ChromaGun
Cities: Skylines - Nintendo Switch Edition
Closed Nightmare
ClusterPuck 99
Clustertruck
Code Realize - Saikou no Hanataba
Code of Princess EX
Coffin Dodgers
Conga Master Party
Constructor Plus
Cosmic Star Heroine
Coven and Labyrinth of Refrain
Crash Bandicoot Buttobi 3-Dan Mori! Bonus Edition
Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy
Crash Dummy
Crawl
Crayola Scoot
Crimsonland
Crossing Souls
Crypt of the Necrodancer
Crystal Crisis
Cube Creator X
Cubikolor
Cytus Alpha
DOOM
DOUBLE DRAGON4
Daedalus - The Awakening of Golden Jazz
Daisenryaku Perfect 4.0
Daitoshokan no Hitsujikai - Library Party
Dandara
Danger Mouse
Danmaku Unlimited 3
Darius Cozmic Collection
Dark Souls - Remastered
Dark Witch Music Episode: Rudymical
Darkest Dungeon
Darkest Dungeon - Ancestral Edition
Darksiders - Warmastered Edition
Darts Up
Dawn of the Breakers
De Mambo
Dead Cells
Dead Synchronicity: Tomorrow Comes Today
Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 - Scarlet
Death Mark
Death Road to Canada
Death Squared
Deemo
Deep Ones
Deponia
Destiny Connect
Detective Gallo
Detention
Devious Dungeon
Diablo III - Eternal Collection
Diabolik Lovers - Chaos Lineage
Die for Valhalla!
Dimension Drive
Disc Jam
Disco Dodgeball Remix
Disgaea 1 Complete
Disgaea 5 Complete
Dont Die Mr. Robot DX
Dont Knock Twice
Dont Starve
Dragon Ball FighterZ
Dragon Marked for Death
Dragon Quest Builders
Dragon Quest Builders 2 - Hakaishin Sidoh to Karappo no Shima
DragonBlaze for Nintendo Switch
DragonFangZ
Dragons - Dawn of New Riders
Dragons Dogma - Dark Arisen
Drawful 2
Dream Alone
DroneFight
Dungeon Rushers
Dungeon Stars
Dust: An Elysian Tail
EARTH WARS
EXTREME POKER
Earth Atlantis
Earthlock
Element
Elliot Quest
Embers of Mirrim
Enchanting Mahjong Match
Energy Balance
Energy Cycle
Energy Invasion
Enigmatis 2: The Mists of Ravenwood
Enter the Gungeon
Epic Loon
FANTASY HERO～unsigned legacy～
FAST RMX
FIFA 18
FIFA 19
FINAL FANTASY X X-2 HD Remaster
FINAL FANTASY XV POCKET EDITION HD
FM Touch 2018
FOX n FORESTS
FRAMED COLLECTION
FUN! FUN! Animal Park
Fairune Collection
Fall Of Light - Darkest Edition
Fallen Legion - Rise to Glory
Fallen Legion: Rise to Glory
Fallout Shelter
Family Computer Nintendo Switch Online
Farming Simulator: Nintendo Switch Edition
Fate Extella Link
Fate/EXTELLA (フェイト/エクステラ)
Fe
Fear Effect Sedna
Figment
Fill-a-Pix: Phils Epic Adventure
Fimbul
Fire Emblem Warriors
Firefighters - Airport Fire Department
Firefighters - The Simulation
Fitness Boxing
Flashback
Flat Heroes
Flinthook
Flip Wars
Flipping Death
Flood of Light
Floor Kids
For The King
Fortnite
Fossil Hunters
Frederic 2
Frederic: Resurrection of Music
Freedom Planet
Frost
Fruitfall Crush
FullBlast
FunBox Party
Furi
Furi - Definitive Edition
Fushigi no Gensoukyou TOD - Reloaded
GALAK-Z: Variant S
GREEN
GRIP
GUNBARICH for Nintendo Switch
GUNBIRD for Nintendo Switch
GUNBIRD2 for Nintendo Switch
Gal Gun 2
Gal Metal
Gal Metal!
Game Doraemon Nobita no Getsumen Tansaki
Garage
Gate of Doom
Gear.Club Unlimited
Gear.Club Unlimited 2
Gekido Kintaros Revenge
Gelly Break
Gem Smashers
Gesshizu - Gajigaji Nakama o Sodateyou
Ghost 1.0
Giana Sisters - Twisted Dreams - Owltimate Edition
Ginger: Beyond the Crystal
Girls und Panzer - Dream Tank Match DX
Glaive: Brick Breaker
Go Vacation
GoNNER
God Wars - Nihon Shinwa Taisen
God Wars the Complete Legend
Goetia
Golf Story
Goo no Wakusei
Goosebumps - The Game
Gorogoa
Gotcha Racing 2nd
Gotouchi Tetsudou for Nintendo Switch!!
Graceful Explosion Machine
Grave Danger
Green Game
Grid Mania
Gridd: Retroenhanced
Guilty Gear - 20th Anniversary Edition
Guns Gore and Cannoli
Guts and Glory
HANDY麻雀
Hakuoki Shinkai Fuukaden for Nintendo Switch
Hammerwatch
Hanayaka Nari, Waga Ichizoku Modern Nostalgie for Nintendo Switch
Hand of Fate 2
Happy Birthdays
Harukanaru Toki no Naka De 6 DX
Harvest Life
Harvest Moon: Light of Hope - Special Edition
Has Been Heroes
Hasbro Game Night
Heart and Slash
Hello Kitty Kruisers
Hello Neighbor
Hello Neighbor Hide & Seek
Henry the Hamster Handler
Heroes of the Monkey Tavern
Heroki
Hexologic
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Hou
Hiragana Pixel Party
Hollow
Hollow Knight
Holy Potatoes! A Weapon Shop?!
Hotel Transylvania 3 - Monsters Overboard
Hulu
Human - Fall Flat
Human Resource Machine
Hungry Shark World
Hunting Simulator
Hyper Light Drifter - Special Edition
Hyrule Warriors: Definitive Edition
I and Me
I, Zombie
ICEY
IMPLOSION
INK
INSIDE
INVERSUS Deluxe
Iconoclasts
Ikaruga
Immortal Redneck
In Between
Infernium
Infinite Minigolf
InkSplosion
InnerSpace
Into The Breach
Ironcast
Island Flight Simulator
Its Spring Again
Ittle Dew 2+
JYDGE
Jang-Navi Mahjong Online
Joe Devers Lone Wolf
Johnny Turbos Arcade Caveman Ninja
Johnny Turbos Arcade Sly Spy
Johnny Turbos Arcade Super Burger Time
Johnny Turbos Arcade Two Crude
Johnny Turbos Arcade Wizard Fire
Jotun: Valhalla Edition
Jumping Joe & Friends
Jurassic Pinball
Just Dance 2017
Just Dance 2018
Just Dance 2019
Just Shapes & Beats
KAMIKO
KORG Gadget
KRC
Karaoke JOYSOUND for Nintendo Switch
Katamari Damacy REROLL
Kato Hifumi Kudan Kanshuu - Hifumin no Shogi Dojo
Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes
KeroBlaster
Kid Tripp
Kill The Bad Guy
King Oddball
Kingdom - New Lands
Kiniro no Corda - Octave
Kitten Squad
Knight Terrors
Knights of Pen & Paper 2 - Deluxiest Edition
Knights of Pen and Paper +1 Deluxier Edition
Koi DX
Kona
Kunio-Kun - The World Classics Collection
L.A. Noire
L.A.ノワール
LEGO - Incredible Family
LEGO City Undercover
LEGO DC Super-Villains
LEGO Harry Potter Collection
LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2
LEGO The Incredibles
LEGO Worlds
LIMBO
LUMINES REMASTERED
Labyrinth of Refrain - Coven of Dusk
Langrisser I & II
Lanota
Lapis Re Abyss
Lapis x Labyrinth
Last day of June
Late Shift
Layers of Fear - Legacy
Laytons Mystery Journey Katrielle to Daifugou no Inbou DX
League Of Evil
Legend of Kay - Anniversary
Legendary Eleven
Legendary Fishing
Let's Sing 10
Let's Sing 2018
Let's Sing 2019
Let's Sing 2019 - Hits Francais
Let's Sing 2019 - Mit Deutschen Hits
Letter Quest Remastered
Levels+
Lichtspeer: Double Speer Edition
LifeGoesOn
Lifeless Planet
Light Fall
Little Dragons Café
Little Dragons Café - Himitsu no Ryuu to Fushigi na Shima
Little Friends - Dogs and Cats
Little Friends Dogs and Cats
Little Friends: Dogs & Cats
Little Inferno
Little Nightmares: Complete Edition
Lode Runner Legacy
Lost Phone Stories
Lost Sea
Lovers in a Dangerous Spacetime
Ludo Mania
Lulua no Atelier - Arland no Renkinjutsushi 4
Lumo
MAHJONG Deluxe 3
MEMBRANE
MIGHTY GUNVOLT BURST
MUJO
MXGP3: The Official Motocross Videogame
Mad Carnage
Mahjong Solitaire Refresh
Makai Senki Disgaea 5
Makai Senki Disgaea Refine
Mama ni Game Kakusareta
Manticore - Galaxy on Fire
Mantis Burn Racing
Maria The Witch
Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle
Mario + Rabbids: Kingdom Battle
Masters of Anima
Max - The Curse of Brotherhood
Mecho Tales
Mega Man 11
Mega Man Legacy Collection
Mega Man Legacy Collection 2
Mega Man X Legacy Collection
Mega Man X Legacy Collection 2
Megaton Rainfall
Memories Off - Innocent Fille for Dearest
Mercenaries Saga Chronicles
Mercenary Kings Reloaded
Metropolis: Lux Obscura
Midnight Deluxe
Miles and Kilo
Millie
Minecraft
Minecraft - Story Mode - Season Two
Minecraft: Nintendo Switch Edition
Minecraft: Story Mode - The Complete Adventure
Mini Metro
Minit
Minna no Dobutsu Shogi
Mom Hid My Game!
Monkey King: Master of the Clouds
Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom
Monster Dynamite
Monster Energy Supercross - The Official Videogame
Monster Energy Supercross - The Official Videogame 2
Monster Energy Supercross: The Official Videogame
Monster Hunter - Generations - Ultimate
Monster Jam - Crush It!
Monster Jam: Crush It!
Moon Hunters
Moonfall Ultimate
Moonlighter
Moorhuhn Remake
Morphies Law
Morphite
Mortal Kombat 11
Mosaic Art Fill a Pix Deluxe
Moto Racer 4
MotoGP 18
Mr Shifty
Muddledash
Mugsters
Mulaka
Mummy Pinball
Mushroom Wars 2
Musou Orochi 3
Musynx
Mutant Football League - Dynasty Edition
Mutant Mudds Collection
My Hero One's Justice
My Little Riding Champion
My Riding Stables - Life with Horses
My Time at Portia
MyFarm 2018
N++ (NPLUSPLUS)
NARUTO SHIPPUDEN: Ultimate Ninja STORM 3 Full Burst
NARUTO SHIPPUDEN: Ultimate Ninja STORM TRILOGY
NARUTO-ナルト- 疾風伝 ナルティメットストームトリロジー
NARUTO: Ultimate Ninja STORM
NBA 2K Playgrounds 2
NBA 2K18
NBA 2K19
NBA Playgrounds
NEKO Para Vol.1
NO THING
NORN9 LOFN for Nintendo Switch
NORTH
NOT A HERO
Namco Museum
Namco Museum Arcade Pac
Nari Kids Park - Kaitou Sentai Lupinranger VS Keisatsu Sentai Patranger
Nari Kids Park - Ultraman R B
Neko-Tomo
Nelke & the Legendary Alchemists - Ateliers of the New World
Nelke to Densetsu no Renkinjutsushi Tachi - Aratana Daichi no Atelier
Neo Atlas 1469
Neon Chrome
Neonwall
NeuroVoider
Never Stop Sneakin
Neverout
New Frontier Days -Founding Pioneers-
New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe
Next Up Hero
Nickelodeon Kart Racers
Nickelodeon Paw Patrol - On A Roll Marshall
Niconico
Night Trap - 25th Anniversary Edition
Night in the Woods
Nightmare Boy
Nights of Azure 2: Bride of the New Moon
Nightshade/百花百狼 / ゲーム
Nihilumbra
Nine Parchments
Ninja Shodown
Ninja Striker!
Ninjin: Clash of Carrots
Nintendo Entertainment System - Nintendo Switch Online
Nintendo Labo - Toy-Con 01: Variety Kit
Nintendo Labo - Toy-Con 02: Robot Kit
Nintendo Labo - Toy-Con 03: Vehicle Kit
Nintendo Labo - Toy-Con 04: VR Kit
No Heroes Here
Nobunaga no Yabou - Taishi with Power-Up Kit
Nora to Oujo to Noraneko Heart 2
Nora to Oujo to Noraneko Heart HD
Nuclien
ONE PIECE アンリミテッドワールドR デラックスエディション
OPUS Collection
OPUS: The Day We Found Earth
Observer
Oceanhorn - Monster of Uncharted Seas
Octocopter: Double or Squids
Octodad: Dadliest Catch
Octopath Traveler
Odallus
Oekaki Puzzle Pic a Pix Deluxe
Oh...Sir! The Hollywood Roast
Oh...Sir!! The Insult Simulator
Old Mans Journey
Old School Musical
One Eyed Kutkh
One More Dungeon
One Piece - Pirate Warriors 3 - Deluxe Edition
One Strike
Oniken
Onimusha - Warlords
Operacion Triunfo 2017
Ostwind - Das Spiel
Othello
Out Of The Box
Outlast
Outlast 2
Overcooked! 2
Overcooked: Special Edition
Owlboy
Oxenfree
PAC-MAN CHAMPIONSHIP EDITION 2 PLUS
PAN-PAN A tiny big adventure
PEACH BALL 閃乱カグラ
PHANTOM BREAKER:BATTLE GROUNDS OVER DRIVE
PLANET ALPHA
POISOFTs "Thud"
Packet Queen #
Paladins
Panda Hero
Pankapu
Paper Wars
Paranautical Activity
Party Arcade
Party Golf
Party Planet
Pato Box
Payday 2
Peach Ball - Senran Kagura
Penguin Wars
Penny-Punching Princess
Perception
Perfect Angle
Phantasy Star Online 2 Cloud
Phantom Trigger
Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney Trilogy
Physical Contact: 2048
Physical Contact: Picture Place
Physical Contact: Speed
Pic-a-Pix Deluxe
Picross S
Picross S2
Piczle Lines DX
Piczle Lines DX 500 More Puzzles!
Piczle Puzzle Pack 3-in-1
Pikachin-Kit - Game de Pirameki Daisakusen
Pilot Sports
Pinball FX3
Pirate Pop Plus
Pirates: All Aboard!
PixARK
PixelJunk Monsters 2
Plague Road
Plantera
Pocket Rumble
Pode
Poi: Explorer Edition
Pokémon Quest
Pokémon: Let's Go, Eevee!
Pokémon: Let's Go, Pikachu
Poly Bridge
Polygod
Pool Panic
Portal Knights
PriPara - All Idol Perfect Stage!
Prison Architect
Pro Yakyuu Famista Evolution
Professional Construction - The Simulation
Professional Farmer - Nintendo Switch Edition
Project Highrise - Architect's Edition
Project Highrise Architects Edition
Psikyo Collection Vol. 2
Psikyo Collection Vol. 3
Psikyo Collection Vol.1
Psyvariar Delta
Punch Club
Putty Pals
Puyo Puyo Tetris
Puzzle Adventure Blockle
Puzzle Box Maker
Puzzle Puppers
Q.U.B.E. 2
Qbics Paint
Qbik
Quad Fighter K
Quest of Dungeons
R.B.I. Baseball 17
R.B.I. Baseball 18
R.B.I. Baseball 19
RESIDENT EVIL REVELATIONS 2
RICO
RIOT - Civil Unrest
RIVE: Ultimate Edition
RPG Tkool MV Trinity
RXN -Raijin-
Rabbit x Labyrinth - Puzzle Out Stories
Rad Rodgers Radical Edition
Radiation Island
Raging Justice
Rapala Fishing - Pro Series
Rayman Legends: Definitive Edition
Realpolitiks
Red Game Without a Great Name
Refrain no Chika Meikyuu to Majo no Ryodan
Regalia: Of Men and Monarchs - Royal Edition
Reine des Fleurs for Nintendo Switch
RemiLore
RemiLore - Lost Girl in the Lands of Lore
Rento Fortune Monolit
Resident Evil 0
Retro City Rampage DX
Revenant Saga
Reverie - Sweet As Edition
RiME
Riptide GP: Renegade
Road to Ballhalla
Robonauts
Robotics;Notes DaSH
Robotics;Notes Otoku Set
Rock N Racing Grand Prix
Rock N Racing Off Road DX
Rocket Fist
Rocket League
Rocket League Ultimate Edition
Rogue Aces
Rogue Trooper Redux
RollerCoaster Tycoon Adventures
Romancing SaGa 2
Root Letter - Last Answer
Rotating Brave
Runbow
Runbow - Deluxe Edition
Runner3
SD Gundam - G Generation Genesis for Nintendo Switch
SEGA Genesis Classics
SEGA Mega Drive Classics
SENRAN KAGURA Reflexions
SHIFT QUANTUMSHIFT QUANTUM
SKYPEACE
SNK 40th Anniversary Collection
SNK Heroines - Tag Team Frenzy
STAY
STEINS;GATE ダイバージェンシズ アソート
STRIKERS1945 for Nintendo Switch
STRIKERS1945Ⅱ for Nintendo Switch
SWORD ART ONLINE - Hollow Realization Deluxe Edition
SaGa - Scarlet Grace - Hiiro no Yabou
Saints Row: The Third - The Full Package
Salt and Sanctuary
SamuraiAces for Nintendo Switch
San Goku Shi 13 with Power-Up Kit
Satsujin Tantei - Jack the Ripper
Saturday Morning RPG
Sausage Sports Club
Save the Ninja Clan
Schlag den Star - Das Spiel
Scribblenauts Mega Pack
Scribblenauts Showdown
Season Match Bundle - Part 1 and 2
Semblance
Semispheres
Sengoku Musou 4 DX
Senjou no Valkyria 4
Serial Cleaner
Serial Cleaner George no Ura Shigoto
Severed
Shadow Bug
Shantae and the Pirate's Curse
Shantae: Half-Genie Hero Ultimate Edition
Shape Of The World
Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn
Shelter Generations
Shephy
Shiftlings
Shikhondo Soul Eater
Shin Den Ai Nani ga Hoshii no Ema Sakura
Shin Sangoku Musou 7 with Moushouden DX
Shining Resonance Refrain
Shinobi Refle - Senran Kagura
Shio
Shovel Knight: Specter of Torment
Shovel Knight: Treasure Trove
Shu
Shut Eye
Sid Meier's Civilization VI
Sigi - A Fart for Melusina
Silence
Sine Mora EX
Skee-Ball
Skies of Fury
Sky Force Reloaded
Sky Gamblers: Storm Raiders
Sky Ride
Sky Rogue
Skylanders - Imaginators
Slain
Slain - Back from Hell
Slayaway Camp: Butchers Cut
Sleep Tight
Slice Dice & Rice
Slime-san
Slime-san Superslime Edition
Smoke and Sacrifice
Snake Pass
Sniper Elite V2 Remastered
Snow Moto Racing Freedom
Soccer Slammers
SolDivide for Nintendo Switch
Soldam: Drop, Connect, Erase
Songbringer
Sonic Forces
Sonic Mania
Sonic Mania Plus
South Park: The Fractured But Whole
Space Dave
Space Ribbon
Spacecats with Lasers
Sparkle 2
Sparkle 2 Evo
Sparkle 3: Genesis
Sparkle Unleashed
Sparkle Zero
Spartan
Spectrum
Spellspire
Spelunker Party!
Sphinx and the Cursed Mummy
Spider Solitaire F
Spintires - MudRunner - American Wilds
Spiral Splatter
SpiritSphere DX
Splasher
Splatoon 2
Sports Party
Spot The Difference
Squareboy vs Bullies: Arena Edition
Star Ghost
Stardew Valley
Starlink: Battle for Atlas
Starship Avenger Operation: Take Back Earth
State of Anarchy: Master of Mayhem
State of Mind
SteamWorld Dig
SteamWorld Heist: Ultimate Edition
Steamworld Dig 2
Steins;Gate Elite
Steredenn
Stern Pinball Arcade
Steven Universe - Save the Light
Stick It to the Man
Stikbold! A Dodgeball Adventure DELUXE
Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection
Streets of Red : Devils Dare Deluxe
Subarashiki Kono Sekai Final Remix
Subsurface Circular
Suicide Guy
Super Beat Sports
Super Blackjack Battle II Turbo - The Card Warriors
Super Bomberman R
Super Chariot
Super Daryl Deluxe
Super Destronaut DX
Super Dragon Ball Heroes - World Mission
Super Inefficient Golf
Super Mario Maker 2
Super Meat Boy
Super One More Jump
Super Ping Pong Trick Shot
Super Putty Squad
Super Robot Taisen T
Super Robot Wars T
Super Sportmatchen
Super Volley Blast
Superbeat: Xonic
Superola and the lost burgers
Surgeon Simulator CPR
Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido
Sword Art Online: Hollow Realization Deluxe Edition
Syberia
Syberia 1 & 2
Syberia 2
Syberia 3
TENGAI for Nintendo Switch
THE Variety Game Daishugo
THE 体感！スポーツパック ～テニス・ボウリング・ゴルフ・ビリヤード
THE 密室からの脱出 ～運命をつなぐ35の謎～
TINY METAL
Tactical Mind
Taiko no Tatsujin - Drum 'n' Fun!
Taiko no Tatsujin - Nintendo Switch Version!
Taishou x Alice: All in One
Tales of Vesperia: Definitive Edition
Tales of the Tiny Planet
Tallowmere
Tantei Jinguuji Saburou Prism of Eyes
Tanzia
Team Sonic Racing
Tennis
Tennis World Tour
Tennis in the Face
Tesla vs Lovecraft
Teslagrad
Tetras Escape
The Adventure Pals
The Adventures of Elena Temple
The Banner Saga Trilogy
The Binding of Isaac - Afterbirth+
The Binding of Isaac: Afterbirth+
The Book of Unwritten Tales 2
The Bridge
The Caligula Effect - Overdose
The Coma - Recut
The Count Lucanor
The Darkside Detective
The Elder Scrolls V - Skyrim
The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim
The End Is Nigh
The Escapists 2
The Escapists: Complete Edition
The Fall
The Fall Part 2: Unbound
The Final Station
The Flame In The Flood Complete Edition
The Flame in the Flood
The Infectious Madness of Doctor Dekker
The Inner World
The Inner World - The Last Wind Monk
The Jackbox Party Pack
The Jackbox Party Pack 2
The Jackbox Party Pack 3
The Jackbox Party Pack 4
The Journey Down: Chapter One
The Journey Down: Chapter Three
The Journey Down: Chapter Two
The LEGO Movie 2 Videogame
The LEGO NINJAGO Movie Video Game
The Liar Princess and the Blind Prince
The Lions Song
The Long Reach
The Longest Five Minutes
The Lost Child
The Low Road
The Mahjong
The Men of Yoshiwara: Kikuya
The Men of Yoshiwara: Ohgiya
The Messenger
The Mooseman
The Mummy Demastered
The Mystery of the Hudson Case
The Nameko no Puzzle - Nameko Dai Hanshoku
The Next Penelope
The Pinball Arcade
The Princess Guide
The Raven Remastered
The Sexy Brutale
The Trail: Frontier Challenge
The VideoKid
The Voice of Germany
The Walking Dead
The Walking Dead - The Final Season
The Wardrobe
The Warlock of Firetop Mountain
The Way Remastered
The World Ends With You -Final Remix-
Them Bombs
Thimbleweed Park
This Is the Police 2
This War of Mine - Complete Edition
This is the Police
Thumper
Timberman VS
Time Recoil
Tiny Barbarian DX
Tiny Hands Adventure
Tiny Troopers Joint Ops XL
Titan Quest
Toby: The Secret Mine
Toki
Toki Tori
Toki Tori 2+
TorqueL -Physics Modified Edition-
Totes the Goat
Touhou Genso Wanderer - Reloaded
Touhou Kobuto V: Burst Battle
Tower Of Babel
Toy Stunt Bike: Tiptops Trials
Trailblazers
Transcripted
Travis Strikes Again - No More Heroes
Treadnauts
Treasure Stack
Trials Rising
Troll and I
Truberbrook
Trueberbrook
TumbleSeed
Tumblestone
Twin Robots: Ultimate Edition
Typoman
UNO
UglyDolls An Imperfect Adventure
Ultimate Runner
Ultra Hyperball
Ultra Space Battle Brawl
Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers
Ultra Street Fighter II: The Final Challengers
Umihara Kawase Fresh!
UnExplored - Unlocked Edition
Unbox: Newbie's Adventure
Undertale
Unepic
Unholy Heights
Unravel Two
Urban Trial Playground
Use Your Words
Usotsuki Hime to Moumoku Ouji
Uurnog Uurnlimited
V-Rally 4
VA-11 HALL-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action
VSR: Void Space Racing
VVVVVV
Vaccine
Valkyria Chronicles 4
Vegas Party
Vesta
Victor Vran - Overkill Edition
Violett
Vostok Inc.
Vroom in the night sky
Völgarr the Viking
WWE 2K18
Waku Waku Sweets
WarGroove
Warriors Orochi 4
Wasteland 2: Directors Cut
Wer Weiss Denn Sowas
West of Loathing
Wheels of Aurelia
Wild Guns Reloaded
Windjammers
Windstorm
Windstorm Aris Arrival
Winning Post 8 2017
Winning Post 9
Wizard of Legend
Wizard's Symphony
Wolfenstein II - The New Colossus
Wonder Boy - The Dragon's Trap
Wonder Boy: The Dragon's Trap
Woodle Tree
Woodle Tree Adventures
Word Search by POWGI
Work x Work
World Conqueror X
World Soccer Pinball
World of Final Fantasy Maxima
World of Goo
World to the West
WorldNeverland - Elnea Kingdom
WorldNeverland-ElneaKingdom-
Worldend Syndrome
Worms W.M.D.
Wulverblade
X-Morph: Defense
Xenoblade Chronicles 2
Xenoblade Chronicles 2: Torna - The Golden Country
Xenon Racer
Xenoraid
Xeodrifter
YU-NO - Kono Yo no Hate de Koi o Utau Shoujo
Yesterday Origins
Yoku's Island Express
Yomawari - The Long Night Collection
Yomawari to Shin Yomawari
Yonder - The Cloud Catcher Chronicles
Yono and the Celestial Elephants
Yooka-Laylee
Yoshi's Crafted World
Yoshiwara Higanbana Kuon no Chigiri
YouTubers Life OMG!
Ys VIII - Lacrimosa of DANA
Ys VIII: Lacrimosa of Dana
Yunohana SpRING! Mellow Times
Yōdanji
ZEROGUNNER2- for Nintendo Switch
ZOMBIE GOLD RUSH
Zaccaria Pinball
Zoids Wild - King of Blast
Zombillie
de Blob
de Blob 2
forma.8
Ōkami HD
あなたの四騎姫教導譚
いけにえと雪のセツナ
いっしょにチョキッと スニッパーズ プラス
すみっコぐらし あつまれ！すみっコタウン
すみっコぐらし すみっコパークへようこそ
なりキッズパーク　HUGっと！プリキュア
ぷよぷよテトリス S
みんなでワイワイ！スペランカー
よるのないくに2 ~新月の花嫁~
わくわくどうぶつランド
わくわくスイーツ あまい おかしができるかな?
ウイニングポスト8 2018
カプコン ベルトアクション コレクション
カーズ3 勝利への道
ギア・クラブ アンリミテッド
シャンティ:ハーフ・ジーニー ヒーロー アルティメット・エディション
ストリートファイター 30th アニバーサリーコレクション インターナショナル
スナックワールド トレジャラーズ ゴールド
スーパー マリオパーティ
スーパーマリオ オデッセイ
ゼノブレイド2
ゼルダの伝説 ブレス オブ ザ ワイルド
ゼルダ無双 ハイラルオールスターズ
ソニックフォース
チームソニックレーシング
ドラゴンクエストヒーローズI•II for Nintendo Switch
ドラゴンボール ゼノバース2
ドンキーコング　トロピカルフリーズ
ニル・アドミラリの天秤 色ドリ撫子
ハッピーバースデイズ
バイオハザード リベレーションズ アンベールド エディション
バイオハザード0 HDリマスター
ファイアーエムブレム無双
ファーミングシミュレーター Nintendo Switch Edition
ポッ拳 POKKÉN TOURNAMENT DX
マリオカート8 デラックス
マリオテニス エース
メモリーズオフ -Innocent Fille-
モノポリー for Nintendo Switch
モンスターハンターダブルクロス Nintendo Switch Ver.
リディー＆スールのアトリエ ～不思議な絵画の錬金術士～
レイマン　レジェンド for Nintendo Switch
レゴ (R) マーベル スーパー・ヒーローズ2 ザ・ゲーム
レゴ ニンジャゴー ムービー ザ・ゲーム
ロストスフィア
ロックマンX アニバーサリー コレクション
ロックマンX アニバーサリー コレクション 2
ローラーコースタータイクーン・アドベンチャー
ワンピース 海賊無双３ デラックスエディション
ヴォイズ
三国恋戦記~オトメの兵法! ~
仮面ライダー クライマックス スクランブル ジオウ
信長の野望・創造 with パワーアップキット
信長の野望・大志
大乱闘スマッシュブラザーズ SPECIAL
戦国無双 真田丸
星のカービィ
最终幻想12：黄道时代
死印 (しいん)
無双OROCHI2 Ultimate (アルティメット)
真・三國無双7 Empires
私立ベルばら学園 ～ベルサイユのばらRe*imagination～
聖剣伝説コレクション
蒼き雷霆 ガンヴォルト ストライカーパック
進め!キノピオ隊長
進撃の巨人２
遊んで将棋が強くなる! 銀星将棋DX